<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Astross</string>
    <string name="aries">Aries</string>
    <string name="tauro">Taurus</string>
    <string name="geminis">Gemini</string>
    <string name="cancer">Cancer</string>
    <string name="leo">Leo</string>
    <string name="virgo">Virgo</string>
    <string name="libra">Libra</string>
    <string name="escorpio">Scorpio</string>
    <string name="sagitario">Sagitarius</string>
    <string name="capricornio">Capricorn</string>
    <string name="acuario">Aquarius</string>
    <string name="piscis">Pisces</string>
    <string name="aries_f">21 Mar - 20 Apr</string>
    <string name="tauro_f">21 Apr - 20 May</string>
    <string name="geminis_f">21 May - 20 Jun</string>
    <string name="cancer_f">21 Jun - 20 Jul</string>
    <string name="leo_f">21 Jul - 20 Aug</string>
    <string name="virgo_f">21 Aug - 20 Sep</string>
    <string name="libra_f">21 Sep - 20 Oct</string>
    <string name="escorpio_f">21 Oct - 20 Nov</string>
    <string name="sagitario_f">21 Nov - 20 Dec</string>
    <string name="capricornio_f">21 Dec - 20 Jan</string>
    <string name="acuario_f">21 Jan - 19 Feb</string>
    <string name="piscis_f">20 Feb - 20 Mar</string>
    <string name="sdiario">Daily horoscope</string>
    <string name="ssemanal">Week horoscope</string>
    <string name="scomp">Compatibility</string>
    <string name="snum">Lucky numbers</string>
    <string name="sfondos">Wallpapers</string>
    <string name="spnl">PNL</string>
    <string name="srecom">" Refer this item to a friend"</string>
    <string name="about">About of …</string>
    <string name="aries_elemento">Fire</string>
    <string name="aries_descripcion">An Aries is a person full of energy and enthusiasm. Pioneer and adventurer, he loves challenges, freedom and new ideas. The Aries like to lead and prefer to give instructions to receive them. They are independent and concerned about their own ambition and goals. They have an enviable energy that sometimes leads them to be aggressive, restless, argumentative, stubborn. It is easy to offend the Aries and, when they feel offended, it is difficult to make peace with them.</string>
    <string name="tauro_elemento">Earth</string>
    <string name="tauro_descripcion">Taurus is usually practical, decisive and has great willpower. Taurus are stable and conservative people, and they will follow loyally a leader they trust. They love peace and tranquility and are very respectful of the laws and rules. They respect material values ​​and avoid debts. They are a bit reluctant to change.</string>
    <string name="tauro_cualidades">Paciente, persistente, decidido y fiable. A un tauro le encanta sentirse seguro. Tiene buen corazón y es muy cariñoso. A tauro le gusta la estabilidad, las cosas naturales, el placer y la comodidad. Los tauro disfrutan con tiempo para reflexionar y les encanta sentirse atraído hacía alguien. </string>
    <string name="tauro_defectos">" Jealous and possessive, a taurus may tend to be inflexible and resentful. Sometimes the Taurus sin of being greedy and allowing it all. Taurus does not like interruptions or rushing. Nor do Taurus like false things. They do not like to feel pressured and can not stand being at home too long."</string>
    <string name="geminis_elemento">Air</string>
    <string name="geminis_descripcion">Gemini is the sign of the twins and as such their character is double and quite complex and contradictory. On the one hand it is versatile, but on the other it can be insincere. They tend to have elegance and fall into the mistakes of young people. They have happiness, self-centeredness, imagination and restlessness in children. The Gemini start new activities and challenges with enthusiasm, but many times they lack the constancy to carry them out. They consider that life is like a game and they look for fun and new situations.</string>
    <string name="geminis_cualidades">" Adaptability and versatility. Gemini are intellectual, eloquent, affectionate, communicative and intelligent. They have a lot of energy and vitality. A Gemini likes to talk, read, do several things at once. They enjoy different and novel things. The more variety in your life, the better."</string>
    <string name="geminis_defectos">" Superficiality and inconstancy. Gemini tend to be nervous and tense at times and can become calculating and demanding. Gemini does not like loneliness. Feeling tied to a situation or a place. He does not enjoy learning at school, but he also does not like to be mentally inactive."</string>
    <string name="cancer_elemento">Water</string>
    <string name="cancer_descripcion">The character of a cancer is the least clear of all the signs of the zodiac. A cancer can be from shy and boring to bright and famous. Cancer is conservative and they love the security and warmth of their home. In fact for men cancer, their home is like a nest, a refuge to go to when the stress of their work is too much. The house of a Cancer tends to be your personal refuge rather than a showcase to dazzle others.</string>
    <string name="cancer_cualidades">Cancer is emotional and affectionate, protective and friendly. A Cancer has a lot of imagination and intuition. You know to be cautious when needed. Cancer likes his house, the countryside, the children. He likes to enjoy his hobbies and he likes parties. A cancer also likes romance.</string>
    <string name="cancer_defectos">Cancer has a tendency to bad mood, they are calculating, disorderly and self-compassionate. Changes his mood and is very susceptible. He struggles to leave a situation. A cancer does not like failure, advice or conflict situations. He does not like people who take the opposite, or to tell him what he has to do.</string>
    <string name="leo_elemento">Fire</string>
    <string name="leo_descripcion">They have ambition, strength, courage, independence and total security in their abilities. They do not usually have doubts about what to do. They are leaders without complications - they know where they want to go and they put all their effort, energy and creativity into achieving their goal. They do not fear obstacles - rather they grow before them.</string>
    <string name="leo_cualidades">Generous and kind, faithful and affectionate. A leo is creative and enthusiastic and understanding with others. He likes adventure, luxury and comfort. A leo enjoys children, theater and parties. The risk motives him too.</string>
    <string name="leo_defectos">Overbearing and bossy. It can be intolerant and dogmatic. It tends to interfere when it should not. Leo does not like vulgar and everyday life. Escape from selfish and ill-conceived people and do not like routine or security.</string>
    <string name="virgo_elemento">Earth</string>
    <string name="virgo_descripcion">Virgo, the only sign represented by a woman, is a sign characterized by its precision, its conventionality, its reserved attitude and its eagerness, sometimes even obsession, with cleanliness. Virgos are often observers and patients. They can sometimes seem cold, and in fact they have a hard time making great friends.</string>
    <string name="virgo_cualidades">Modesty, intelligence and shyness. Virgo are usually meticulous, practical and hardworking. They have great analytical capacity and are reliable. Virgo likes healthy living, making lists, order and hygiene.</string>
    <string name="libra_elemento">Air</string>
    <string name="libra_descripcion">Libra are among the most civilized signs of the zodiac. They have charm, elegance and good taste, and are friendly and peaceful. They like beauty and harmony and are able to be impartial in conflicts. However, once they have reached an opinion about something, they do not like to be contradicted. They like to have the support of others.</string>
    <string name="libra_cualidades">" Diplomatic, charming and sociable. Libra are idealists, pacifists, optimists and romantics. They have a gentle and balanced character."</string>
    <string name="libra_defectos">They are undecided and easily influenced by third parties. They can change their opinion easily and be too complacent.</string>
    <string name="escorpio_elemento">Water</string>
    <string name="escorpio_descripcion">Scorpio is an intense sign with a unique emotional energy throughout the zodiac. Although they may seem calm, the Scorpios have an internal magnetism hidden inside. They are affable, good tertulianos, reserved and polite, but although they seem to be something withdrawn from the activity center, in fact they are observing everything with their critical eye.</string>
    <string name="escorpio_cualidades">Emotional, determined, powerful and passionate. Scorpio is a sign with a lot of magnetism. Scorpio likes the truth, work when it makes sense, get involved in causes and convince others.</string>
    <string name="escorpio_defectos">Jealous, compulsive and obsessive. The scorpions can be resentful and stubborn. A Scorpio does not like the superficial, meaningless relationships. He does not accept easy compliments and does not support people teasing him.</string>
    <string name="sagitario_elemento">Fire</string>
    <string name="sagitario_descripcion">Sagittarius is one of the most positive signs of the zodiac. They are versatile and love adventure and the unknown. They have an open mind to new ideas and experiences and maintain an optimistic attitude even when things get difficult. They are reliable, honest, good and sincere and willing to fight for good causes at all costs.</string>
    <string name="sagitario_cualidades">Intellectual, honest, sincere and friendly. Sagittarians are characterized by optimism, modesty and good humor. Saita likes freedom, travel, adventure and the ability to understand.</string>
    <string name="sagitario_defectos">They are so optimistic at times that they become irresponsible. Superficial, careless and restless. Sagittarius does not like being tied to a situation, having to worry about the details.</string>
    <string name="capricornio_elemento">Earth</string>
    <string name="capricornio_descripcion">Capricorn is one of the most stable, safe and calm signs of the zodiac. They are workers, responsible and practical and willing to persist until necessary to achieve their objective. They are reliable and often have the role of finishing a project initiated by one of the most pioneering signs. They love music.</string>
    <string name="capricornio_cualidades">Capricorn are ambitious, disciplined, practical, prudent, and patient. They have a good sense of humor and are reserved. A Capricorn likes reliability, professionalism, a solid foundation, having a goal, leadership.</string>
    <string name="capricornio_defectos">Capricorn tends to be pessimistic and, in difficult situations, even fatalistic. Sometimes it costs him to be generous with others and it costs him to do favors altruistically. A Capricorn does not like impractical plans, fantasize, ridiculous, or frivolous people.</string>
    <string name="acuario_elemento">Air</string>
    <string name="acuario_descripcion">Aquariums have a strong and attractive personality. There are two types of aquariums: one is shy, sensitive, and patient. The other type of aquarium is exuberant, alive and can hide the depths of its personality under a frivolous air. Both types of aquariums have a very strong conviction and truth and they are so honest that they know how to change their opinions if there is evidence that shows the opposite of what they thought before.</string>
    <string name="acuario_cualidades">Aquarians like to fight for good causes, dream and plan a happy future, learn from the past, they are good friends and they like to have fun. The aquariums are nice and humane. They are honest, loyal, original and brilliant. An aquarium is independent and intellectual.</string>
    <string name="acuario_defectos">An aquarium does not like promises to the air, nor to feel alone. An aquarium is unpredictable and tends to be contrary. It is not emotional and does not understand the emotional complexity of some people and not the betrayal between friends.</string>
    <string name="piscis_elemento">Water</string>
    <string name="piscis_descripcion">Pisces have a quiet personality, patient and kind. They are sensitive to the feelings of others and respond with sympathy and tact to the suffering of others. They are very dear to others because they have an affable, affectionate and kind character, and do not pose a threat to those who want positions of authority or greater popularity.</string>
    <string name="piscis_cualidades">Imaginative and sensitive. He is friendly and has compassion for others. It\'s intuitive and think of others. Pisces likes to be alone to dream. He likes the mystery and the absurd. He likes to get lost.</string>
    <string name="piscis_defectos">It does not assume reality. It is idealistic, keeps secrets and has a somewhat weak will. It is carried away by others. Pisces does not like the obvious, nor do they like to be criticized, nor do people like to be pedantic or believe.</string>
    <string name="aries_diario">Planets support you all you need to cut your ties and go to the bottom of things today. The planets are creating some resistance for the subjects of the race you can think that you do not progress as much as you would like. You do not have the patience to get online today. Your attention should be turned towards a creative or business project. The conditions are particularly propitious now and you should not miss the opportunity. You go fast in your career and it drives you crazy what you do. You have time for something else and you run the risk of things losing their balance.</string>
    <string name="aries_semana">This week your message comes through the letter of God, reminding you that the limits are only in your imagination and that heavenly help is on the way to fulfill your best wishes. In love, refocus and look for new possibilities that will give you greater growth and happiness.</string>
    <string name="tauro_diario">Be honest with yourself and with others today regardless of the pressures you feel. Just thinking about money causes you disgust but putting your head in the sand is not a solution. Your mood returns after a short period of uncertainty. Be optimistic and your career plans will take off. You may have to discover some deception or fraud within your workplace, so it is important to be alert and have an action plan. The square made by the Moon and Mars does not make things easy for you in this regard.</string>
    <string name="tauro_semana">This week your angel recommends keeping the chosen path, since soon you will begin to enjoy the honeys of success. Job offers will be the order of the day, although it will be better to take a reasonable time before giving an answer. In love, your suitors will grow like foam pay attention to the signs!</string>
    <string name="geminis_diario">There are good prospects to take on a long-term challenge No matter how difficult it may be, you will be able to get ahead. It\'s time to accept that times have changed. The ball is not in the same yard anymore. The rules are new and you have to learn them by heart. An unexpected opportunity can appear in a professional situation, meaning that you must be prepared to jump to any opportunity. If you keep your faith in yourself with your achievements in sight things will be reconciled and can not go wrong. And he will not do it out of love, but out of pure and hard pride.</string>
    <string name="geminis_semana">This week your angel recommends prioritizing family issues related to the health of parents or children in your home. Keep the caution and provide the support that your loved ones require. In love, planning is good, but the action is what will make the difference in front of your partner.</string>
    <string name="cancer_diario">Expect very positive changes with regard to work you will find yourself in a new work situation more and more satisfactory. this is one of those moments. The conditions for a risk under long-term investments, property sales and inheritances are good. Do not throw yourself with the first person who crosses your path just because you need affection or attention. Exercising gives him a lot of laziness, but do you have any idea what will make him happy to be able to do so many abs? Out of laziness and to rejuvenate your health.</string>
    <string name="cancer_semana">Faith first and foremost This week your angel recommends you stay away from unfair situations and environments where they do not give you the value you deserve. Better opportunities will open before your eyes if you have the courage to take distance. In the emotional aspect, although you hesitate to return, do not give second chances to those who have hurt you in the past.</string>
    <string name="leo_diario">There is competition at work a superior is playing the game of a rival of yours. that attempt at provocation can be an offer of love in disguise. Be firm and clearly state that you are not willing to stand with folded arms. It is a kind of race against time now when someone asks you for help you will deny it. The action by impulse is excluded today will place you in an uncomfortable position.</string>
    <string name="leo_semana">This week your angel predicts a great opportunity to get support and help from influential beings. Your growth has no limits, if you believe in your qualities. Contract signatures can be given optimally towards Thursday. In love, you will have the possibility of giving a higher level of commitment to your relationship.</string>
    <string name="virgo_diario">Keep a close eye on your finances. You can come into conflict with someone who can interrupt your progress at least for the time being. There are sure symptoms that you are burning stages In one minute you learn new traps and in the other you are teaching them to others. Professional matters are charged, even overwhelming, you must take them forward to the best of your ability. Believe it or not despite your esp + irita independent you better join forces with someone for professional reasons.</string>
    <string name="virgo_semana">This week your angel predicts pleasant moments in the company of your loved ones, because meetings and social encounters will give a broader meaning to your life. The work aspect will begin to improve, making you allies and admirers of your talent. In the emotional aspect, the relationship with your partner will take a very positive direction.</string>
    <string name="libra_diario">Hay grandes cambios en puerta para tí en todos los aspectos en los próximos meses estás fuertemente avisado para que lo tomes con calma y te prepares para tiempos difíciles. El la vida hay algo mas que sòlo trabajo, trabajo y trabajo Algo ocurre hoy que te recuerda que es hora de espabilarte y gozar de la vida. Los viajes, la carrera y las finanzas están íntimamente vinculados puede ser que se presente una oportunidad en la carrera. Las finanzas juegan un creciente papel en tu actual línea de pensamiento Toma ventaja de la situación y mira a ver cómo puedes mejorar tu seguridad a largo plazo. Hoy es un día para recuperar recuerdos.</string>
    <string name="libra_semana">This week your angel recommends you to resist with some uncomfortable situations in the work area. Keep prudence, but defend your ideas with great firmness. In love, many sentimental options may defocus you from true love, avoid temptation!</string>
    <string name="escorpio_diario">You are willing to admit that you have made a mistake. You do not have to publish it. Others will make things look their way You will not stubbornly but you will keep your positions. Just wanting, waiting and dreaming is not enough to go where you want Take a concrete action. Financial decisions made today can prove to be an excellent investment for the future. If you feel like it, go ahead, do not think about it.</string>
    <string name="escorpio_semana">Closure of cycles. This week your angel recommends starting the process of closing all those issues that do not allow you to grow in the future. You will make important decisions in the workplace that will allow for major changes. In love, a stage closes, preparing you for a new beginning.</string>
    <string name="sagitario_diario">If you act on a whim, you will end up acquiring something at a premium or that it is not worth it. Some restraint is needed, at least in matters of money. You have an infinite source of courage that will help you in hard times. The astral forces encourage you to forget your obligations today you can estimate that the compromises with your career are a burden, and your attention deviates easily. A dilemma can be resolved if you propose to apply your powers of concentration and analysis. Pleasant encounters will restore confidence in others</string>
    <string name="sagitario_semana">Independence. This week your angel recommends managing your big projects in an autonomous way, because you have enough talent to achieve great things with your own impulse. In love, let your intuition continue to guide you regarding the decisions you must make with your partner.</string>
    <string name="capricornio_diario">You are radiant, you conquer and your vital attitude is so positive and optimistic that we all want to get close to you in case some of your energy hits us. In your House five will bring up the competitive and impetuous player who bets up underwear in the field of love. This will increase your popularity to produce effects that will surprise you. Maybe it comes from the hand of a job that complements the one you already have. You are touched by the magic wand of the word, so take advantage of it.</string>
    <string name="capricornio_semana">" Patience. This week your angel recommends keeping your anxiety levels under control, as some delays could make you see things in an uncertain way. God's time is perfect, allowing processes to be completed, in order to advance safely in your professional field. In love, when so many obstacles arise, it is better to meditate on the appropriateness of the relationship."</string>
    <string name="acuario_diario">You want to get ahead but you also want to make others happy. That means a hard balance and compromise is essential. Others may make more noise than you but you are the owner of your serenity and independence. It is easier than you think. Thanks for the good things you have and there will be better things. If others do not openly acknowledge you, you will be disappointed and assume the position and privileges that you consider appropriate.</string>
    <string name="acuario_semana">" Positive connection This week your angel recommends not delegate to big projects, if you want to get results out of series. Your angels will give you the energy necessary to undertake challenges, which only a true leader like you can overcome. In love, you will feel a magical connection with someone you are beginning to know, let it flow!"</string>
    <string name="piscis_diario">Charge the batteries and make sure your appearance is the best. When new responsibilities come to you, do not fear. You are more than capable of assuming them and there will be someone willing to lend a hand if necessary. The fun is over for a while now you must dedicate yourself to an old and hard work. Acts and collects the benefits. They need time and patience.</string>
    <string name="piscis_semana">" Expansion. This week your angels predict a positive movement in your work area, which will help you increase your income and improve your professional conditions. Start your routine with the best energy and likewise the results will not wait. In love, stability as a couple has come to stay in your life for a good time. Enjoy all the blessings that only true love can give you."</string>
    <string name="elemento">Element:</string>
    <string name="descripcion">Description:</string>
    <string name="virtudes">Righteousness</string>
    <string name="defectos">Defect:</string>
    <string name="enero">January</string>
    <string name="febrero">February</string>
    <string name="marzo">March</string>
    <string name="abril">April</string>
    <string name="mayo">May</string>
    <string name="junio">June</string>
    <string name="julio">July</string>
    <string name="agosto">August</string>
    <string name="septiembre">September</string>
    <string name="octubre">October</string>
    <string name="noviembre">November</string>
    <string name="diciembre">December</string>
    <string name="horoscopodel">Horoscope of</string>
    <string name="de">of</string>
    <string name="del">of</string>
    <string name="delD">Of</string>
    <string name="al">at</string>
    <string name="deD">Of</string>
    <string name="a">to</string>
    <string name="compatibilidadpor">\?%</string>
    <string name="es">is</string>
    <string name="compatiblecon">compatibility with</string>
    <string name="numeros_de_suerte">" lucky number"</string>
    <string name="chance">Play the chance</string>
    <string name="baloto">Play the baloto</string>
    <string name="Frases">phrase of the day</string>
    <string name="recomendar_des">If this application was to your liking, do not hesitate to recommend it, enter a contact\'s email and press the send button.</string>
    <string name="recomendar">Recommend</string>
    <string name="enviado">The recommendation has been sent to the email:</string>
    <string name="vacio">" You must type an email"</string>
    <string name="correonovalido">The email is not valid</string>
    <string name="pnl1">" Be clear that at the top you will not get ahead of others, but surpassing yourself."</string>
    <string name="pnl2">Never let your fears take the place of your dreams..</string>
    <string name="pnl3">Life was not about being a winner or a loser, it was about being oneself and giving the best.</string>
    <string name="pnl4">It is never too late to try to achieve what you really always wanted.</string>
    <string name="pnl5">" It is possible that the fall is inevitable, but continuing on the ground will always be optional."</string>
    <string name="pnl6">" Learn not to give up and be constant, the beginning is the hardest part."</string>
    <string name="pnl7">" The challenge of my life was not other than discovering how far I could go by doing what I liked"</string>
    <string name="pnl8">" Go with confidence in the direction of your dreams. Live the life you have imagined."</string>
    <string name="pnl9">" We are what we repeatedly do. Excellence then, is not an act but a habit."</string>
    <string name="pnl10">The only thing that stands between a man and what he wants out of life is often simply the willingness to try and the faith to believe that it is possible</string>
    <string name="pnl11">" Sometimes losing is winning and not finding what you are looking for is to find yourself."</string>
    <string name="aries_cualidades">They like adventure and challenges. An Aries likes to win and be spontaneous. He also likes to give his support to a good cause. Adventurous and energetic, the Aries are pioneers and brave. They are smart, dynamic, confident and tend to show enthusiasm for things.</string>
    <string name="aries_defectos">" He does not like to wait. The Aries can not bear to fail or be wrong, and do not accept with good pleasure the advice of others. Nor do tyrants admit. They can be selfish and have genius. The Aries are impulsive and sometimes have little patience. They tend to take too many risks."</string>
    <string name="virgo_defectos">Conservative and perfectionist, a Virgo tends to worry too much and his hard side can lead him to be overly critical and hard on others. Virgo does not like dirt, disorder, danger, vague people, uncertainty.</string>
    <string name="pnl12">The challenge of my life was no other than discovering how far I could go by doing what I liked.</string>
    <string name="prefijo_idioma">en</string>
    <string name="title_activity_splash">SplashActivity</string>
</resources>
